Guide to the McCann-Erickson Worldwide vertical files, 1914-1997 and undated RL.11412
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
McCann-Erickson Worldwide vertical files
1914-1997 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
McCann-Erickson Worldwide
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11412
111.0 Linear Feet
McCann Erickson Worldwide is an American advertising agency founded in 1930, now part of the Interpublic Group of Companies. It is headquartered in New York. The collection consists of reference files by topic. The files include research reports, periodicals, maps, clippings, brochures and other printed materials. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized numerically by topic classification.
Biographical / Historical
McCann-Erickson formed in 1930 from a merger of the H.K. McCann Company and the Erickson Company. The agency formed the core of the holding company Interpublic Group of Companies in 1961 and is currently active as a subsidiary of Interpublic. The vertical files were originally maintained by the McCann-Erickson Library, later by the Center for Advertising Service, then the Center for Market Intelligence (CMI) a subsidiary of Interpublic.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The McCann-Erickson Worldwide vertical files were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2008.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company Advertising vertical files J. Walter Thompson Company Marketing vertical files
Collection Overview
The collection spans 1914-1997 with the bulk of materials spanning 1926-1979 and consists of reference files by topic. The files include research reports, periodicals, maps, clippings, brochures and other printed materials. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Vertical Files, 1914-1997 and undated; 1
  - 1A: Business conditions (Forecasts, indexes, Gross National Product), 1950-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1A: Business conditions (Forecasts, indexes, Gross National Product), 1976 (Box 52)
  - 2A: Market data--Spanish, 1971-1977 (Box 1)
  - 2A: Market data--Women, 1957-1975 (Box 1)
  - 2B-1: Population--Census data (Marriages, families, households), 1940-1978 (Box 1)
  - 2B-3: Population--Vital statistics, 1964-1977 (Box 1)
  - 2B-3: Population--Vital statistics, 1964-1977 (Box 2)
  - 2B-3: Population--Vital statistics (Marriage, birth, divorce), 1965-1977 (Box 2)
  - 2B-3: Population--Vital statistics (Geriatrics), 1964-1966 (Box 2)
  - 2C: Income (Personal, families), 1951-1978 (Box 2)
  - 2D: Youth market, 1958-1976 (Box 2)
  - 2D: Youth market, 1951-1978 (Box 3)
  - 2D: Youth market, 1967-1971 (Box 52)
  - 2D: Youth market--Seventeen Magazine reports, 1972-1976 (Box 3)
  - 2E: Financial/Economy, 1933-1978 (Box 3)
  - 2F: Price Index/Cost of living, 1940-1977 (Box 3)
  - 2G-1: Business--Capital expenditures, 1944-1977 (Box 3)
  - 2G-2: Business--Industry, 1959-1977 (Box 3)
  - 2G-3: Business--Wages and employment, 1948-1978 (Box 3)
  - 2G-3: Business--Wages and employment, 1948-1978 (Box 4)
  - 2H: Business--Consumer attitudes/Spending, 1932-1978 (Box 4)
  - 2I: Business--International (Trade, investment, balance of payments), 1957-1978 (Box 4)
  - 2J: Business--Farm data, 1947-1978 (Box 4)
  - 2K: Business--Business failure, 1947-1974 (Box 4)
  - 2L: Business--Negro market, 1942-1977 (Box 4)
  - 2M: Business--Office and business management, 1952-1976 (Box 4)
  - 2N: Business--Corporate acquisition/Mergers, 1948-1978 (Box 5)
  - 3A: Corporate--Robinson Patman Act, 1936 (Box 5)
  - 3A: Corporate--Legal issues, 1927-1976 (Box 5)
  - 3B: Corporate--Advertising liability, 1937-1941 (Box 5)
  - 3C: Corporate--Patent and copyright, 1930-1977 (Box 5)
  - 3D: Corporate--Taxes, 1956-1971 (Box 5)
  - 3D: Corporate--Taxes--DuPont, The Story of Taxes, 1957 (Box 52)
  - 4A: Commercial and trade organizations, 1957-1973 (Box 5)
  - 4C: American Management Association publications, 1964-1974 (Box 5)
  - 5A: Marketing--Marketing practice, 1957-1978 (Box 5)
  - 5A: Marketing--Marketing practice, 1957-1978 (Box 6)
  - 5A: Marketing--McCann Erickson, Management Work of Marketing in a Durable Goods Business, 1951 (Folder 1)
  - 5B: Marketing--Cooperative marketing, 1943-1963 (Box 6)
  - 5B: Marketing--Cooperative marketing, 1962 (Box 52)
  - 5C: Marketing--Premiums/Consumer profit-sharing/Trading stamps, 1919-1979 (Box 6)
  - 5C: Marketing--Premiums/Consumer profit-sharing/Trading stamps, 1976-1979 (Box 52)
  - 5C: Marketing--Goodwin Plan, 1933-1939 (Box 6)
  - 5E: Marketing--Installment sales/Credit cards, 1939-1977 (Box 6)
  - 5G-1: Buying habits, 1930-1979 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1A: Buying influence surveys, 1933-1977 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1A: Buying influence surveys, 1961-1968 (Box 53)
  - 5G-1D: Wage Earner Forum, 1961-1963 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1E: Brand Habits of American Families, 1950 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1E: Modern Magazine Survey of Health and Beauty Products, 1934-1959 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1E: Modern Magazine Survey of Homemaking, 1941-1952 (Box 7)
  - 5G-1E: Modern Magazine Survey of Homemaking, 1941-1952 (Box 8)
  - 5G-1E: Modern Magazine Survey of Housekeeping/Housekeeping Habits, 1938-1940 (Box 8)
  - 5G-2: Retail, 1951-1970 (Box 8)
  - 5G-4: Retail--Television advertising--Brand comparisons, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
  - 5H: Retail--Samples and demonstrations, 1949-1963 (Box 8)
  - 5J: Retail--Trade-in offers, 1947-1957 (Box 8)
  - 5K: Retail--Trading areas (Market testing, research), 1947-1979 (Box 9)
  - 6A: Distribution, 1946-1968 (Box 9)
  - 6B: Mailing lists/Direct marketing, 1946-1978 (Box 9)
  - 6D: Broker/Jobber/Wholesale, 1937-1974 (Box 9)
  - 6E: Discounter/Discount retail, 1952-1978 (Box 9)
  - 6F: Retail, 1961-1975 (Box 9)
  - 6F-1: Retail merchandising, 1952-1978 (Box 10)
  - 6G: Department stores, 1948-1978 (Box 10)
  - 6G: Department stores, 1963 (Box 52)
  - 6I: Variety stores, 1952-1978 (Box 10)
  - 6I: Variety stores, 1961 (Box 52)
  - 6I: Variety stores--Chain variety stores map, 1960 (Folder 1)
  - 6J: Vending machines, 1949-1974 (Box 10)
  - 6K: Telephone sales, 1939-1978 (Box 10)
  - 7A: Sales--Organization and management, 1947-1978 (Box 10)
  - 7B: Sales--Salesman training, 1947-1978 (Box 11)
  - 7C: Sales--Salesmen compensation, 1950-1976 (Box 11)
  - 7D: Sales--Sales contests, 1929-1975 (Box 11)
  - 7E: Sales--Sales conventions, 1945-1971 (Box 11)
  - 7F: Sales--Sales quotas, 1927-1972 (Box 11)
  - 7G: Sales--Sales forecasting, 1929-1970 (Box 11)
  - 9A: Brands and trademarks, 1923-1979 (Box 11)
  - 9E: Brands--National brands, 1947-1977 (Box 11)
  - 9F: Brands--Private labels, 1949-1977 (Box 12)
  - 9H: Brands--Corporate name changes, 1942-1977 (Box 12)
  - 10: Packaging, 1944-1978 (Box 12)
  - 10: Packaging--Multi-packs, 1958 (Box 12)
  - 12A: Research--General, 1939-1976 (Box 12)
  - 12B-1: Research--Marketing research/Psychographics, 1935-1979 (Box 12)
  - 12B-1: Research--Marketing research/Psychographics, 1935-1979 (Box 13)
  - 12B-2: Research--Consumer testing/surveys, 1935-1965 (Box 13)
  - 12C: Research--Media research/Dassault Awards, 1948-1978 (Box 13)
  - 12E: Research--Product research, 1947-1974 (Box 13)
  - 13: Research--Sampling, 1939-1979 (Box 13)
  - 14: New products/Product development, 1938-1979 (Box 13)
  - 14: New products/Product development, 1938-1979 (Box 14)
  - 14: New products/Product development, 1938 (Box 54)
  - 15B-1: Advertising in wartime, 1940-1944 (Box 14)
  - 15B-1: Advertising in wartime--Committee on Public Information, Government War Advertising, 1918 (Box 55)
  - 15B-1: Advertising in wartime--World War II posters, circa 1943 (Folder 1)
  - 16: Automation, 1953-1970 (Box 14)
  - 20A: Advertising--General, 1935-1979 (Box 14)
  - 20A: Advertising--General, 1972 (Box 55)
  - 20B: Advertising--History, 1925-1968 (Box 15)
  - 20B: Advertising--History, 1956-1959 (Box 55)
  - 20B: Advertising--History--A Century of Town and Country Advertising, 1946 (Box 55)
  - 20B: Advertising--History--Ladies Home Journal 75 Years of Advertising to Women, 1958 (Box 55)
  - 20B: Advertising--History--The Story of Advertising poster, 1944 (Folder 1)
  - 20D: Advertising--Awards, 1931-1971 (Box 15)
  - 20D: Advertising--Awards--Harvard Advertising Awards (1926-1930), Andy (1966, 1926-1966 (Box 55)
  - 20E: Advertising--Recruitment, 1948-1976 (Box 15)
  - 20F: Advertising--Regulation/Consumer protection/False and misleading advertising, 1940-1979 (Box 15)
  - 20G: Advertising--Continuity, 1941-1976 (Box 15)
  - 21: Advertising--Psychology/Motivation, 1948-1973 (Box 16)
  - 22: Advertising--Economic justification, 1929-1978 (Box 16)
  - 25: Advertising--International, 1944-1978 (Box 16)
  - 28B-1: Advertising--Agency billings, 1935-1971 (Box 17)
  - 28C: Advertising--Cooperative, 1935-1979 (Box 17)
  - 29A: Advertising--Copy, 1930-1976 (Box 17)
  - 29B: Advertising--Long vs. short copy, 1925-1975 (Box 17)
  - 29C: Advertising--Copy appeals, 1924-1978 (Box 17)
  - 29E: Advertising--Seasonal copy, 1928-1964 (Box 17)
  - 29F: Advertising--Advertorials, 1949-1968 (Box 18)
  - 29G: Advertising--Slogans, 1925-1967 (Box 18)
  - 29H: Advertising--Testimonials and celebrity endorsements, 1929-1978 (Box 18)
  - 29I: Advertising--American Way of Living, 1954-1976 (Box 18)
  - 29I: Advertising--Institutional/Corporate, 1937-1978 (Box 18)
  - 29J: Advertising--Advertising and product quality, 1932-1947 (Box 18)
  - 29K: Advertising--Copy testing, 1926-1979 (Box 18)
  - 29K: Advertising--Copy testing, 1942 (Box 55)
  - 47: Advertising--Magazines and magazine advertising, 1945-1976 (Box 18)
  - 48: Advertising--Newspapers and newspaper advertising, 1945-1977 (Box 18)
  - 48: Advertising--Newspapers and newspaper advertising, 1964 (Box 55)
  - 49: Advertising--Business papers, 1948-1967 (Box 19)
  - 50: Advertising--Direct, Point of sale, 1949-1975 (Box 19)
  - 100A: Food--Distribution costs, 1941-1954 (Box 19)
  - 100D: Food--Grocery brokers/Wholesale, 1928-1969 (Box 19)
  - 100E: Food--Independent grocers/Wagon jobbers, 1928-1976 (Box 19)
  - 100F: Food--Grocery chain stores/Supermarkets/Grocery shopping habits, 1933-1979 (Box 19)
  - 100G: Food--Food service industry, 1945-1971 (Box 19)
  - 101A: Food and nutrition--General data/Recipes, 1931-1979 (Box 19)
  - 101A: Food and nutrition--General data/Recipes, 1963 (Box 56)
  - 101C: Food and nutrition--Infant care and feeding, 1939-1979 (Box 20)
  - 101D: Food and nutrition--Weight control and diet, 1935-1970 (Box 20)
  - 101E: Food and nutrition--Health and mortality/Vitamins, 1937-1979 (Box 20)
  - 102A: Foods--Processed food, 1948-1979 (Box 20)
  - 102B: Foods--Syrup/Molasses/Honey, 1934-1976 (Box 20)
  - 102C: Foods--Frozen food, 1929-1979 (Box 20)
  - 102C: Foods--Frozen food, 1929-1979 (Box 21)
  - 102D: Foods--Dietetic, 1962-1979 (Box 21)
  - 103D: Foods--Rice, 1932-1978 (Box 21)
  - 103E: Foods--Shortening, 1930-1978 (Box 21)
  - 103F: Foods--Cereals, 1930-1979 (Box 21)
  - 104A: Foods--Canned, 1944-1979 (Box 22)
  - 104B: Foods--Canned fruits, 1930-1979 (Box 22)
  - 106A: Foods--Meats, 1927-1979 (Box 22)
  - 106B: Foods--Fish and seafood, 1929-1978 (Box 22)
  - 107A: Foods--Baking products, general, 1926-1978 (Box 22)
  - 107A: Foods--Baking products, general, 1926-1978 (Box 23)
  - 107A: Foods--Baking products, vitamin-fortified bread and flour, 1931-1958 (Box 23)
  - 107B: Foods--Bread, 1929-1979 (Box 23)
  - 107C: Foods--Crackers, 1929-1979 (Box 23)
  - 107D: Foods--Cakes and snack foods, 1934-1976 (Box 23)
  - 107E: Foods--Dog and pet food, 1934-1979 (Box 23)
  - 107E: Foods--Dog and pet food--Edwin Colbert, Origin of the Dog, 1939 (Box 56)
  - 107F: Foods--Flour mixes, 1937-1978 (Box 23)
  - 108A: Foods--Fresh fruits and vegetables, 1943-1966 (Box 23)
  - 108B: Foods--Fresh fruit, 1926-1978 (Box 24)
  - 108B: Foods--Fresh fruit--Citrus, 1965 (Box 56)
  - 108C: Foods--Vegetables, 1927-1973 (Box 24)
  - 108D: Foods--Nuts, 1932-1978 (Box 24)
  - 109A: Beverages--General, 1929-1979 (Box 24)
  - 109B-1: Beverages--Coffee, 1927-1972 (Box 24)
  - 109B-1: Beverages--Coffee, 1960-1979 (Box 25)
  - 109B-1: Beverages--Coffee--Pan American Coffee Bureau, 1954-1976 (Box 25)
  - 109B-3: Beverages--Coffee makers (appliances), 1933-1975 (Box 25)
  - 109C: Beverages--Tea, 1928-1983 (Box 25)
  - 109D: Beverages--Cocoa and chocolate, 1932-1978 (Box 25)
  - 109D: Beverages--Soft drinks, 1927-1960 (Box 25)
  - 109D: Beverages--Soft drinks, 1961-1979 (Box 26)
  - 110E: Ice cream, 1958-1977 (Box 26)
  - 111A: Household--Cleansers and scouring pads, 1929-1979 (Box 26)
  - 111B: Household--Cleaning fluids, 1945-1974 (Box 27)
  - 111D: Household--Soaps and detergents, 1930-1979 (Box 27)
  - 111D: Household--Soap and Detergent Association, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
  - 112A: Pharmaceutical--General, 1932-1957 (Box 27)
  - 112G: Pharmaceutical--Drugs, wholesale, 1948-1961 (Box 27)
  - 112G: Pharmaceutical--Drugs, wholesale, 1962 (Box 56)
  - 112G: Pharmaceutical--Drugs, wholesale--Area maps, 1948 and undated (Folder 1)
  - 112H: Pharmaceutical--Drugs, retail, 1961-1977 (Box 27)
  - 112H: Pharmaceutical--Drugs, retail--Drug Topics: What the Public Spends for Drug Store Products, 1949-1964 (Box 27)
  - 113A: Drugs--General, 1933-1979 (Box 28)
  - 113B: Drugs--Antiseptics, disinfectants, mouthwash, 1927-1978 (Box 28)
  - 113C: Drugs--Proprietary medicines, 1929-1979 (Box 28)
  - 113D: Drugs--Skin care, topical medications, 1938-1978 (Box 28)
  - 113E: Drugs--First aid products, 1933-1963 (Box 28)
  - 113F: Drugs--Laxatives, 1922-1977 (Box 28)
  - 113G: Drugs--Cough and cold remedies, 1934-1979 (Box 28)
  - 113H: Drugs--Feminine hygiene, 1961-1979 (Box 28)
  - 114A: Toilet goods--General, 1941-1978 (Box 29)
  - 114A: Toilet goods--General, 1979 (Box 56)
  - 114B: Toilet goods--Hand lotions, 1953-1978 (Box 29)
  - 114B: Toilet goods--Hand lotions, 1967 (Box 56)
  - 114C: Toilet goods--Perfumes, 1926-1979 (Box 29)
  - 114D: Toilet goods--Cosmetics, 1931-1979 (Box 29)
  - 114E: Toilet goods--Dental preparations, oral hygiene, 1938-1979 (Box 29)
  - 114E: Toilet goods--Dental preparations, oral hygiene, 1938-1979 (Box 30)
  - 114F: Toilet goods--Hair care, 1933-179 (Box 30)
  - 114G: Toilet goods--Toilet, bath soap, 1927-1979 (Box 30)
  - 114H: Toilet goods--Men's toiletries, shaving products, 1937-1971 (Box 30)
  - 114H: Toilet goods--Men's toiletries, shaving products, 1930-1979 (Box 31)
  - 114H: Toilet goods--Men's toiletries, shaving products, 1966 (Box 56)
  - 114I: Toilet goods--Deodorants and depilatories, 1928-1979 (Box 31)
  - 114J: Toilet goods--Manicure, nail products, 1938-1979 (Box 31)
  - 115B-1: Transportation--Automobile Facts and Figures, 1922-1939 (Box 31)
  - 115B-1: Transportation--Automobile Facts and Figures, 1940-1975 (Box 32)
  - 115B-2: Transportation--Production and finance statistics, 1934-1949 (Box 32)
  - 115C: Transportation--Automobiles, 1954-1979 (Box 32)
  - 115C: Transportation--Automobiles, 1937-1979 (Box 33)
  - 115C: Transportation--Automobiles--Studebaker, 100 Years on the Road, 1952 (Box 56)
  - 115C: Transportation--Automobiles--Ford at Fifty, 1953 (Box 57)
  - 115C: Transportation--Automobiles--Buick's First Half Century, 1953 (Box 57)
  - 115C-1: Transportation--Rental cars, 1947-1979 (Box 34)
  - 115D: Transportation--Trucks and recreational vehicles, 1936-1978 (Box 34)
  - 115E: Transportation--Bus travel, 1965 (Box 34)
  - 115F: Transportation--Motor boats, 1928-1977 (Box 34)
  - 115G-1: Transportation--Automotive equipment and service, 1935-1978 (Box 34)
  - 115G-2: Transportation--Tires, 1928-1979 (Box 34)
  - 115I: Transportation--Motor vehicle laws, 1936-1965 (Box 34)
  - 115J: Transportation--Used cars, 1922-1965 (Box 34)
  - 116: Petroleum and fuels--General, 1951-1977 (Box 35)
  - 116A: Petroleum and fuels--Petroleum Facts and Figures, 1959-1971 (Box 35)
  - 116A: Petroleum and fuels--A Great Name in Oil, Sinclair Through Fifty Years, 1966 (Box 57)
  - 116B: Petroleum and fuels--American Petroleum Institute, 1960 (Box 35)
  - 116A: Petroleum and fuels--American Petroleum Institute, Telling the Centennial Story Portfolio for Women in Radio and TV, 1959 (Box 57)
  - 116C: Petroleum and fuels--Gasoline, Gas stations, 1930-1979 (Box 35)
  - 116D-1: Petroleum and fuels--Gasoline, 1927-1974 (Box 36)
  - 116E: Petroleum and fuels--Lubricants, motor oil, 1933-1978 (Box 36)
  - 116F: Petroleum and fuels--Heating oil, 1945-1974 (Box 36)
  - 116H: Petroleum and fuels--LP gas, 1931-1967 (Box 36)
  - 117: Hardware, hardware stores, 1943-1975 (Box 36)
  - 120A: Textiles--General, 1933-1977 (Box 36)
  - 120E: Textiles--Linens and domestics, 1941-1974 (Box 36)
  - 120F: Textiles--Cotton, 1929-1974 (Box 36)
  - 120G: Textiles--Wool, 1949-1975 (Box 36)
  - 120H: Textiles--Silk, 1926-1963 (Box 36)
  - 120J: Textiles--Synthetics, 1938-1973 (Box 36)
  - 121A: Clothing--General, 1956-1973 (Box 36)
  - 121A: Clothing--General, 1932-1979 (Box 37)
  - 121A: Clothing--Men's wear, 1958-1973 (Box 37)
  - 121B: Clothing--Zippers, 1939-1971 (Box 37)
  - 121C: Clothing--Hats, 1929-1979 (Box 37)
  - 121D: Clothing--Hosiery, 1931-1978 (Box 37)
  - 121E-1: Clothing--Boots and shoes, 1930-1979 (Box 37)
  - 121E-3: Clothing--Sneakers, 1928-1938 (Box 37)
  - 121E-4: Clothing--Shoe soles, inserts, 1928-1955 (Box 37)
  - 121E-5: Clothing--Shoe polish, cleaners, 1936-1964 (Box 37)
  - 121F: Clothing--Underwear, intimate apparel, 1942-1976 (Box 37)
  - 121G: Clothing--Children's, infant wear, 1935-1974 (Box 37)
  - 122A: Housing--Construction industry, 1949-1978 (Box 37)
  - 122A: Housing--Construction industry, 1954-1978 (Box 38)
  - 122A: Housing--Statistics, 1948-1977 (Box 38)
  - 124B: Travel and transport--Railroads, 1940-1975 (Box 38)
  - 124C: Travel and transport--Steamships, 1930-1974 (Box 38)
  - 124D: Travel and transport--Air, Airlines, 1963-1976 (Box 38)
  - 124D: Travel and transport--Air, Airlines, 1935-1977 (Box 39)
  - 124E: Travel and transport--Trucking, 1952-1979 (Box 39)
  - 124F: Travel and transport--Bus lines, 1931-1978 (Box 39)
  - 125A: Insecticides, pesticides, 1945-1979 (Box 39)
  - 125B-1: Pesticides, 1927-1967 (Box 39)
  - 125B-2: Household insects and pests, 1914-1967 (Box 39)
  - 125B-4: Animal insects, 1920-1946 (Box 39)
  - 126A: Office equipment and machines, 1940-1970 (Box 40)
  - 126C: Writing materials, stationery, 1934-1979 (Box 40)
  - 126G: Publishing, books, 1932-1978 (Box 40)
  - 127A: Tobacco, 1934-1976 (Box 40)
  - 127A: Tobacco, 1927-1976 (Box 41)
  - 127A: Tobacco, 1964-1979 (Box 42)
  - 127B: Photographic equipment, 1935-1979 (Box 42)
  - 127M-5: Bicycles, mopeds, motorcycles, 1931-1978 (Box 42)
  - 127N: Fertilizers, 1950-1976 (Box 42)
  - 127O: Glass, 1932-1979 (Box 42)
  - 127P: Metals, 1943-1976 (Box 42)
  - 127Q: Musical instruments, 1940-1974 (Box 42)
  - 127R: Matches, 1942-1976 (Box 42)
  - 127S: Coal, 1933-1977 (Box 43)
  - 127T: Tools, 1934-1979 (Box 43)
  - 127U: Minerals, 1960-1972 (Box 43)
  - 127V: Lawn and garden, 1938-1979 (Box 43)
  - 127V: Lawn and garden, 1963-1973 (Box 57)
  - 127W: Plastics, 1953-1975 (Box 43)
  - 127X: Home security, 1970-1979 (Box 43)
  - 128A: Tourism--Community advertising, 1929-1976 (Box 43)
  - 128B: Tourism--Florida, 1951-1968 (Box 43)
  - 128C: Tourism--Foreign, 1946-1972 (Box 43)
  - 129A: Financial--General, 1934-1979 (Box 43)
  - 129B: Financial--Banks, 1961-1978 (Box 43)
  - 129B: Financial--Banks, 1943-1979 (Box 44)
  - 129C: Financial--Insurance, 1954-1978 (Box 44)
  - 129E: Financial--Corporate annual reports (reporting genre, not individual company reports), 1959-1977 (Box 44)
  - 129E: Financial--Corporate annual reports (reporting genre, not individual company reports), 1963 (Box 57)
  - 130A: Public utilities--Electric, gas, 1935-1976 (Box 45)
  - 130B: Public utilities--Telephone, telegraph, 1927-1979 (Box 45)
  - 131: National advertising, 1927-1977 (Box 45)
  - 132A: Electronics--General, 1942-1978 (Box 45)
  - 132B: Supermarket broadcast advertising, 1946-1957 (Box 45)
  - 132C-1: Radio, 1926-1979 (Box 45)
  - 132C-2: Radio broadcasting, 1935-1979 (Box 45)
  - 132D: Television, color television, 1951-1978 (Box 45)
  - 132D-1: Television--Television sets, video, 1945-1978 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Broadcasting, 1938-1979 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Educational, 1959-1967 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Telecasting, 1960-1974 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Pay televisin, cable, 1964-1977 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Commercials (including subliminal, comparative), 1957-1978 (Box 46)
  - 132D-2: Television--Vs. other media, 1935-1972 (Box 46)
  - 132E: FM radio, 1940-1976 (Box 46)
  - 132F: Phonographs, tape recorders, 1939-1979 (Box 46)
  - 132G: Computers, 1954-1978 (Box 47)
  - 133A: Aircraft, 1928-1979 (Box 47)
  - 133B: Aerospace industry, space vehicles, 1957-1977 (Box 47)
  - 134: Hotel, motel, restaurant, 1935-1979 (Box 47)
  - 135: Travel and tourism, 1932-1979 (Box 48)
  - 136B: Beer--Consumption research, 1953-1970 (Box 48)
  - 136B: Beer--Brewers Almanac, 1966-1976 (Box 48)
  - 136B: Beer--Surveys and clippings, 1932-1979 (Box 49)
  - 136B: Beer--Statistics, pre-sterilization, 1955-1971 (Box 49)
  - 137: Motion pictures, 1935-1979 (Box 49)
  - 138A: Energy, energy policy, 1969-1974 (Box 49)
  - 138A: Energy, energy policy, 1960-1978 (Box 50)
  - 138B: Nuclear energy, 1935-1979 (Box 50)
  - 499: Miscellaneous, 1929-1979 (Box 50)
  - 499B: Education, 1931-1977 (Box 50)
  - 499E: Religion, 1953-1971 (Box 50)
  - 499H: Natural resources, 1955-1975 (Box 50)
  - 499K: Management consultants, 1958-1973 (Box 50)
  - 499O: Military service, 1947-1978 (Box 50)
  - Unnumbered files--Automobiles, sporty, 1990-1997 (Box 51)
  - Unnumbered files--Automobiles, subcompact, 1991-1996 (Box 51)
  - Unnumbered files--Motorcycles, mopeds, 1990-1997 (Box 51)
  - Unnumbered files--Motor oil, 1991-1997 (Box 51)
  - Unnumbered files--Information requests, 1990-1995 (Box 51)